Guide to the Wunderman Archives, 1946-2010 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Training and Presentation Materials, 1974-2002 and undated, (54 boxes)
  - Young & Rubicam (Y&R)
    - Coaching for Results, 1997 (Box TR39)
    - Creative Work Plan training program, 1993 (Box TR39)
    - Effective Management (Cindy Butchko), 1996, (1-2 of 4 folders)
      - Effective Management (Cindy Butchko), 1996, (3-4 of 4 folders) (Box TR40)
    - Effective Presentation Skills, undated, (2 folders) (Box TR40)
    - How We Work, 1987, 1993, (3 folders)
      - Intern Program: Presentation Skills, undated, (2 folders) (Box TR41)
    - Introduction to Y&R Tools, undated, (2 folders) (Box TR41)
    - Lester Wunderman presentation to Y&R Stockholder Meeting (slides removed), 1974 (Box TR41)
    - Listening Skills, 1983 (Box TR41)
    - Negotiating Workshop, 1995 (Box TR41)
    - Performance Management Guidebook, undated (Box TR41)
    - Performance Management Training Program, 1995, (2 folders) (Box TR41)
    - Professional Skills Development Series (PSDS)
      - Being a Y&R Trainer, undated (Box TR42)
      - Better Results Through Listening, undated, (2 folders) (Box TR42)
      - Effective Presentations, trainer guide, undated (Box TR42)
      - Interviewing Skills Workshop, trainer guide, undated (Box TR42)
      - Negotiating Workshop, trainer guide, circa 1995 (Box TR42)
      - People Development Group, Training Coordinator guide, circa 1995 (Box TR42)
      - Running Effective Meetings Workshop, trainer guide, 1992 and undated, (2 folders) (Box TR43)
      - Time Management, 1992, 1996, (2 folders) (Box TR43)
      - Writing Workshop, 1995 and undated, (3 folders) (Box TR43)
    - Proposal for direct marketing videocassette program (Cindy Butchko), 1985 (Box TR43)
    - Selling the Program, 1978-1984 and undated, (2 folders) (Box TR44)
    - Stopping Power self-test kit, undated, (2 folders) (Box TR44)
    - Strategic Planning Disciplines, undated (Box TR44)
    - Strategy Workshop, undated, (2 folders) (Box TR44)
    - Supervisor's Workshop, 1984, 1990, (3 folders) (Box TR45)
    - Supervisory Skills Training Manual, 1984 (Box TR45)
    - Teamwork exercises, undated (Box TR45)
    - Time Management, 1981-1986 and undated, (3 folders) (Box TR45)
    - Training Program Development (Cindy Butchko), 1984 (Box TR46)
    - Training programs and services, undated (Box TR46)
    - Worldwide Training Needs Analysis, 1991 (Box TR46)
  - Y&R/Marsteller
    - Direct Marketing Institute, 1984, (2 folders) (Box TR46)
  - Y&R Resource Center
    - Consultative Selling Skills, 1981 (Box TR46)
    - Helping Clients Buy, 1988 (Box TR46)
    - Meeting notes and agenda, 1988 (Box TR46)
    - Notes from Idea Workshop, 1988 (Box TR47)
    - Results from Meetings Workshop, 1987 (Box TR47)
  - Y&R/Synergenics
    - Client Partnering Skills, 1992 (Box TR47)
  - Y&R/WCJ Team AT&T
    - Phoenix Project training, 1996 (Box TR47)
  - Y&R/Wunderman
    - Direct Marketing Workshop: Listening Skills, 1987 (Box TR47)
  - Y&R/Wunderman/O&M
    - Training materials binder, circa 1988, (3 folders) (Box TR47)
  - Restricted Files
    - Dentsu Y&R
      - Communications Skills Workshop, Langkawi, Malaysia, 1999, (3 folders) (Box TR-R1)
    - Impiric
      - Approaching Direct Mail and Print Results from a Marketing Perspective, circa 2000 (Box TR-R1)
      - Art and Science of Customer Relationships, 2000, (2 folders) (Box TR-R1)
      - Communications Rollout, 2000, (1 of 2 folders) (Box TR-R1)
      - Communications Rollout, 2000, (2 of 2 folders) (Box TR-R2)
      - Direct Marketing and Print Results, circa 2000 (Box TR-R2)
      - Direct Marketing Math, 2000, (2 folders) (Box TR-R2)
      - Email 101, 2000 (Box TR-R2)
      - Global Orientation Plan, circa 2000 (Box TR-R2)
      - Orientation Manual, 2000 (Box TR-R2)
      - Promotion Seminar, 2000 (Box TR-R3)
      - Supervisors Training Program, 2000 (Box TR-R3)
    - Wunderman
      - Global Employee Orientation Manual, 2002 (Box TR-R3)
      - Global Orientation Manual, 2001 (Box TR-R3)
      - iCubed Training Conference, 2002 (Box TR-R3)
      - Intern Program/Mentor Program, 2001 (Box TR-R3)
      - LatAm Direct Marketing Workshop, Tequesquitengo, Morelos, Mexico, 2000 (Box TR-R3)
      - Managing Global Accounts (IBM), 2001 (Box TR-R3)
      - P3 Handbook for Effective Performance Management, 2001 (Box TR-R3)
      - P3 Performance Management Workshop, 2001 (Box TR-R4)
      - Performance Management Workshop, circa 2001, (2 folders) (Box TR-R4)
    - Wunderman Cato Johnson
      - Action Marketing Strategy Development Seminar, 1998 (Box TR-R4)
      - Business Basics, 1998, (2 folders) (Box TR-R4)
      - Creative Brief training, 1998 (Box TR-R4)
      - CRM 101/Bootcamp workshops, 2000 (Box TR-R4)
      - Customer Relationship Management (CRM)--Ericsson, 1999 (Box TR-R5)
      - Marketing Math, 1999 (Box TR-R5)
      - Miami and Puerto Rico training program, 1998 (Box TR-R5)
      - Planning Print Campaigns, 1999 (Box TR-R5)
    - Young & Rubicam (Y&R)
      - Account Executive/Assistant Account Executive (AE/AAE) program, 2000 (Box TR-R5)
      - Advanced Seminar for Advertising Skills
        - Barcelona, 1998, (3 folders) (Box TR-R5)
        - Biography and training survey, 1999 (Box TR-R5)
        - Madrid, 2000, (4 folders) (Box TR-R6)
        - Prague, 1999, (4 folders) (Box TR-R6)
      - Better Results Through Listening, 1998 (Box TR-R7)
      - Negotiating Workshop, 1998 (Box TR-R7)
      - Running Effective Meetings, 1998 (Box TR-R7)
      - Selling Creative Work, 2001, (2 folders) (Box TR-R7)
      - Selling Creative workshop, 1999-2001 (Box TR-R7)
      - Team Y&R Process Play Book, 1998 (Box TR-R7)
      - Thinking Strategically, 1998 (Box TR-R7)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1946-2003 and undated, (122 boxes)
  Includes recorded presentations, spot radio announcements and television commercials, and compilation reels of commercials. Arranged alphabetically by company name and title.
  Restrictions on Access: Original audiovisual materials are closed to research. Research Services must obtain use copies for access.
  - 100 of the Greatest Direct Response Television Commercials. Part B. Undated. VHS. TRT: 60:00 (Box 1)
  - 4-C's Iced Tea. Davis Family campaign spots. 1987, 1990. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 1)
  - @T Home Blacksburg
    - Untitled. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 1)
    - Untitled. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 1)
  - Abril Colecoes video collection (WCJ/MPA-RIO/Brazil).
    - The History of Rock & Roll. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 120:00 (Box 1)
    - The History of Rock & Roll. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 120:00 (Box 1)
  - Abril Livros/Time Life. Biblioteca 425/Gazeta 7000. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 21:00 (Box 1)
  - Access Didn't Know/3 In One. UK spots. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 1)
  - Adelaide Central Mission (Australia). Adelaide Bank/Candlelit Dinner. Undated. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 1:00 (Box 1)
  - Adult Diaper (Japan). Untitled. Undated. VHS. TRT: 1:00 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age. Video presentation. Undated. VHS. TRT: 10:00 (Box 1)
  - Adweek. Best Advertising of 1994. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 120:00 (Box 1)
  - Agrogas (Chile). Radio commercial, English. 1995. VHS. TRT: 1:00 (Box 1)
  - Air France
    - Beauty and the Beast (1946, dir. Jean Cocteau)Circa 1994. VHS. TRT: 90:00 (Box 1)
    - General spots, English version. 1995. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 1:00 (Box 1)
  - America Online. Spots. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 4:10 (Box 1)
  - American Express
    - Adbank compilation. 1988-1991. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 1)
    - Adbank compilation. 1991-1992. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 1)
    - Amex2. 1995. VHS. TRT: 3:00 (Box 1)
    - Amex--RIP. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 1)
    - Best Things in Life. 1991. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 1:00 (Box 1)
  - American Express (Box 2)
    - Bill Miller; Jim Hansen; 2nd Honeymoon; Wallet; Water Ballet; Cityscape; Olympics; Vail. 1977-1992. VHS. TRT: 6:00 (Box 2)
    - Brand campaign: Do More; U. S. Anthem; U. K. Anthem. Undated. VHS. TRT: 3:00 (Box 2)
    - Brazilian campaign, 12 spots. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 12:00 (Box 2)
    - Business First: Continental Airlines. Undated. VHS. TRT: 1:00 (Box 2)
    - C=Amex2. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 2)
    - Challenges. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 2)
    - Challenges. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 2)
    - Competitive and historical spots. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 2)
    - Competitive reel. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 2)
    - Competitive television commercials. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 2)
    - Corporate Card (Spanish). Undated. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 2)
    - Corporate Card: As You Can See--Expense Management. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 2)
    - Corporate Card: As You Can See--Value Savings. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 2)
    - Corporate Card: Greater Success. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 2)
    - Corporate Card: Heart and Soul. Undated. VHS. TRT: 1:00 (Box 2)
    - Corporate Card: Heart and Soul/No Offer/Stereo. 1995. VHS. TRT: 1:00 (Box 2)
    - Corporate Card radio and TV. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 2)
  - American Express (Box 3)
    - Corporate Card: Spirit; National Life Stages; Success; Decision Time; Elaine Sung; New Card Design; Brazil; Company Names/Mexico; Argentina; Aldo Papone. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 10:00 (Box 3)
    - Corporate Card: Success. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 3)
    - Corporate Card: Success/Stills. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 3)
    - Corporate Card: Success '93. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 3)
    - Corporate Card: Success; National Life Stages; Decision Time. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 3)
    - Corporate Card: To Your Success. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 3)
    - Déjà Vu. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 3)
    - Double Head. Undated. VHS. TRT: 3:00 (Box 3)
    - Dreams World Service. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 2:40 (Box 3)
    - Dreams World Service. 1995. Betacam SP. TRT: 2:40 (Box 3)
    - DRTV: National Life Stages; Success '92; Decision Time; Heart and Soul; Challenges; Challenges Gold; Golden Age. 1992-1997. VHS. TRT: 7:00[2 copies] (Box 3)
    - End of the 80s; Small Business; Corporate America; Large and Small Business. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 3)
    - End of the 80s; Small Business; Corporate America; Large and Small Business. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 3)
    - End of the 80s; Small Business; Corporate America; Large and Small Business. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 3:30 (Box 3)
    - End of the 80s; Small Business; Corporate America; Large and Small Business. Undated. VHS. TRT: 3:30 (Box 3)
    - Focus groups current perspectives; interview (Fletcher); Focus groups reactions to creative. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 3)
    - Giant Card; Different View. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 3)
  - American Express (Box 4)
    - Gold Card: Adbank spots. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 4)
    - Gold Card: American Express Gold, Regular. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 4)
    - Gold Card: Bridge; Ripple; Trailblazer; Elusive; Precious; Personal; Envoy. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 6:30 (Box 4)
    - Gold Corporate Card: Opportunities. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 4)
    - Gold Corporate Optima. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 4)
    - Gold Corporate Optima: Golden Age/No Annual Fee. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 4)
    - Golden Age revised. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 4)
    - Greater Success; Spirit; Mail alt. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 4)
    - Greater Success/Spirit: End of the 80s; Small Business; Corporate America; Large and Small Business; You're Not Alone. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 3:30 (Box 4)
    - Greater Success/Spirit rev. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 4)
    - Heart and Soul. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 4)
    - Hire an Assistant. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 0:30[2 copies] (Box 4)
    - Historical reel. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 4)
    - How to Talk to Generation X; C=Amex2. 1994. VHS. TRT: 2:00[2 copies] (Box 4)
    - Jade Albert. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 4)
  - American Express (Box 5)
    - Loyalty. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 0:45 (Box 5)
    - Loyalty. 1995. VHS. TRT: 0:45 (Box 5)
    - Mexico campaign: Company Names; Descriptive. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 3:40 (Box 5)
    - National Life Stages; Success 92; A Su Exito (Puerto Rico); New Card Design (Brazil); Company Names (Mexico); New Face; Patrick Wong; Elaine Sung. Undated. VHS. TRT: 6:00 (Box 5)
    - One Check: Déjà vu. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 5)
    - Optima Card international launch; Mike Becker tape. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 5)
    - Optima: True Grace. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 5)
    - Patrick Wong; Frank Wong; David Ng; Elaine Sung. Undated. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 2:00 (Box 5)
    - Radio TV Reports spots. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 5)
    - Radio TV Reports spots. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 5)
    - Restaurants; Hotels. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 5)
    - SBS Corporate Card: Challenges. 1996. VHS. TRT: 2:00 (Box 5)
    - SBS Corporate Optima: Golden Age. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 5)
    - SBS Corporate Optima: Golden Age. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 4:30 (Box 5)
    - SBS Corporate Optima: Golden Age. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 5)
    - Spirit; To Your Success; Oui Merci. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 5)
  - American Express (Box 6)
    - Standards; Here's to More Life; international spots. 1991. Umatic. PALTRT: 5:00 (Box 6)
    - Standards; Here's to More Life; international spots. Undated. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 2:30 (Box 6)
    - Students That Never Sleep (intern project); 1996. VHS. TRT: 2:00 (Box 6)
    - Success 92; National Life Changes. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 6)
    - Unexpected Pleasures. 1991. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 1:00 (Box 6)
    - Various spots: Father/Daughter; Recital; Operator; Perfect Gift; Island Honeymoon; World Tour; Green Card; Super Bowl. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:50 (Box 6)
    - Y&A (personal). Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 6)
    - Not Wunderman: Jerry Seinfeld, Supermarket. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 6)
  - American Express--Various radio spots
    - Big Card. 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. [2copies] (Box 6)
    - Boardroom. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Brave Music. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. [2 copies] (Box 6)
    - Centurion (3 alternate endings). 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Centurion Latest/Panorama. 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Centurion (music with voiceover). 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. [2 copies] (Box 6)
    - Centurion music. 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Centurion Original/Panorama/Underlined ending. 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Centurion Panorama. 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Corporate America. 1989Audiocassette. TRT: 0:30 (Box 6)
    - Corporate Barriers II. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - End of the 80s; Small Business; Corporate America; Large and Small Business. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: 3:30 (Box 6)
    - Fred Slobodin music: Ray Lynch; Money Mag Telephone; Benny Goodman What Can I Say; Field of Dreams, The Library; Trans Blue. 1990Audiocassette. TRT: 9:36 (Box 6)
    - Greater Success. 1989Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box 6)
    - Joe Diehl Music. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Large and Small Business. 1989Audiocassette. TRT: 0:30 (Box 6)
    - Mix 1--Hot Music. 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Music (4 versions). 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Music demo. 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Music exploratories. 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Music only: Business; Corporate America; Business; Small Business. 19891/4" audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box 6)
    - New Anniversary copy. 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. [2 copies] (Box 6)
    - Reel Diehl Music TV demo. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00[2 copies] (Box 6)
    - Small Business. 1989Audiocassette. TRT: 0:30[2 copies] (Box 6)
    - Success large market. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Success revised, small market. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - The Natural. 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Then and Now. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - Triumph. 1990Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
    - untitled. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 6)
  - American Family Sweepstakes. Adbank compilation. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 6)
  - American Heritage. Richard Reeves. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 4:30 (Box 6)
  - American Tax Service. Wait in Line; Forms and Figures. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 6)
  - Ameritech
    - Buy One Get One; 2nd Service for #2. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 6)
  - Ameritech (Box 7)
    - Call Waiting Busy Signal; 3-Way Calling Music. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 7)
    - Music--Columbus. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 7)
    - Music--Dayton; Busy Signal-Rockford. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 7)
    - Various spots: Caller ID campaign. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 9:00 (Box 7)
  - Andersen Consulting. Fish. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 7)
  - Apple Computer
    - Apple Club (Hong Kong). Undated. VHS. PALTRT: 3:00 (Box 7)
    - Apple Education Reseller Marcom (Europe). 1993. CD-ROM. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 7)
    - Barcelona presentation. 1990. Betacam SP. TRT: 80:00[4 tapes] (Box 7)
    - Creating the PowerBooks; Macintosh vs. Windows. 1991. VHS. TRT: 40:00 (Box 7)
    - Direct Marketing Process Systems and Partnerships. 1990. VHS. TRT: 5:16 (Box 7)
    - In Business with Macintosh. 1990. VHS. TRT: 10:00[2 copies] (Box 7)
    - Kickoff '92. 1992. CD-ROM. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 7)
    - Kids in Room 116 (Canadian version). Undated. VHS. TRT: 28:30 (Box 7)
    - Lester Wunderman; Julie Riegel 1991 Sales Conference. 1990. VHS. TRT: 1:30 (Box 7)
    - Macintosh--The Design Solution. 1993. VHS. TRT: 45:00[2 copies] (Box 7)
    - Macintosh Tag Version. 1993. Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box 7)
    - Performa. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 7)
    - Performa: The Martinelli's Bring Home Their Computer. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 3:00[2 copies] (Box 7)
    - Performa: The Martinelli's Bring Home Their Computer, demo clip. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 2:30 (Box 7)
    - Performa: The Martinelli's Bring Home Their Computer, inquiry. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 28:30 (Box 7)
  - Apple Computer (Box 8)
    - Performa: The Martinelli's Bring Home Their Computer. 1994. VHS. TRT: 3:00 (Box 8)
    - Performa: The Martinelli's Bring Home Their Computer, inquiry. Undated. VHS. TRT: 28:30 (Box 8)
    - Performa: The Martinelli's Bring Home Their Computer, trailer. 1995. VHS. TRT: 4:15 (Box 8)
    - Power family of computers: 1984/Power/Testing 1-2-3/Power. 1991. VHS. TRT: 10:00 (Box 8)
    - Power of Apple Desktop Media. Undated. VHS. TRT: 10:00[2 copies] (Box 8)
    - Seminar for One: Apple/IBM Alliance. Undated. VHS. TRT: 30:00[2 copies] (Box 8)
    - Seminar for One: Connectivity--Networking and Communications in Multivendor Environments. Undated. VHS. TRT: 30:00[2 copies] (Box 8)
    - Seminar for One: IS Issues in the 1990s--The Universal Client. Undated. VHS. TRT: 30:00[2 copies] (Box 8)
    - Seminar for One: Power Macintosh--The New Standard for Business Computing. Undated. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 8)
    - The World of Apple Desktop Media. 1989. VHS. TRT: 10:00 (Box 8)
  - Assitalia. UnaFamily radio spots. 1997. Audiocassette. TRT: 1:30 (Box 8)
  - AT&T
    - Access: Trucker; Military Man/Navy; Military. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 8)
    - Access: Twice the Price. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 8)
    - Access: Twice the Price; Instructional; In My Business. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 1:30[2 copies] (Box 8)
    - Bell Atlantic Long Distance Service: You Don't Have to Feel So Very Far Away; Son Tells Dad About Pitching a Game. 2000. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 8)
    - Bell Atlantic Long Distance Service: You Don't Have to Feel So Very Far Away; Son Tells Dad About Pitching a Game. 2000. VHS. TRT: 1:30 (Box 8)
    - Brand print with end title. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 8)
    - Card: Sydney wrap; Pamela wrap. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 2:00[2 copies] (Box 8)
    - Card Preference: Ted/Guy rev.; Silence rev. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 8)
  - AT&T (Box 9)
    - Canada launch. 1996. VHS. TRT: 5:17 (Box 9)
    - Canada launch: Anthem; True Choice Multi; Call Anywhere; Call Province; Absoposolutely. 1996. VHS. TRT: 5:00[2 copies] (Box 9)
    - Club Directo (Guatemala). 1997. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 9)
    - Concert. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 9)
    - Connections. 1996. Betacam SP. TRT: 2:28 (Box 9)
    - Connections. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 9)
    - Easy Reach animatics. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 9)
    - Easy Reach: Life Changes/Grad (4 versions). 1992. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 9)
    - Group I. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 90:00[2 tapes] (Box 9)
    - Group II. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 90:00[2 tapes] (Box 9)
    - Group III. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 90:00[2 tapes] (Box 9)
    - Group I. 1999. VHS. TRT: 90:00 (Box 9)
    - Group II. 1999. VHS. TRT: 90:00 (Box 9)
    - Group III. 1999. VHS. TRT: 90:00 (Box 9)
    - HFC (9 spots): Hot Dog Stand; Number One New York; Rhett and Scarlett; Switch the Pitcher; Lucky Dog; Twirling Remote; One for Texas. 2000. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 9)
    - HFC teaser. 2000. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 9)
  - AT&T (Box 10)
    - Hot Dog Stand; Number One New York; Rhett and Scarlett; Switch the Pitcher; Twirling Remote. 2000. Umatic. TRT: 5:00[2 copies] (Box 10)
    - Hot Dog Stand; Number One New York; Rhett and Scarlett; Switch the Pitcher; Twirling Remote. 2000. VHS. TRT: 5:00[2 copies] (Box 10)
    - International Military: Fast Talker II. Agency version. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 0:65 (Box 10)
    - Language Line. 1990. VHS. TRT: 5:00 (Box 10)
    - Local/Long Distance: Number One NY rev. 2000. Umatic. TRT: 2:00[2 copies] (Box 10)
    - Local/Long Distance: Number One NY, new supers. 2000. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 10)
    - Local One Rate: Hot Dog Stand. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 10)
    - Local Service: Hot Dog Stand; Number One N. Y. 2000. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 10)
    - Local Service: Hot Dog Stand; Number One N. Y. 2000. VHS. TRT: 1:00 (Box 10)
    - Museo. 1995. VHS. TRT: 0:30 (Box 10)
    - Number One/NY. 2000Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 10)
    - Number One/NY. 2000Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 10)
    - Opportunity Calling. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 8:59 (Box 10)
    - Personal Choice; TVC; Consumer Calling Card. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 10)
    - Reiser rev.; Why Wait?; Joy of Six. 1999. VHS. TRT: 2:00 (Box 10)
    - Segmentation video: Who Are They?1996. VHS. TRT: 10:00 (Box 10)
    - Sprint brand review. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 10)
  - AT&T (Box 11)
    - Swarn Jayanti Sweepstakes (India). 1997. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 11)
    - Taking Our Customers Into The Future. 1999. VHS. TRT: 10:00 (Box 11)
    - The One for Texas. 2000. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 11)
    - The One for Texas. 2000. VHS. TRT: 0:30 (Box 11)
    - Time Warner: Rhett and Scarlett (Avid rough cut). 2000. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 11)
    - Time Warner: Rhett and Scarlett (not final). 2000. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 11)
    - Time Warner: Rhett and Scarlett (version 4). 2000. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 11)
    - Top Dog; Couple; Kathleen; Rocker. 1998. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 11)
    - Trucker; Military Man; Military Man/Navy. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 11)
    - True Connections: Coach NFA Agency reel. Undated. VHS. TRT: 2:00[3 copies] (Box 11)
    - Twice the Price; Instructional; In My Business. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 11)
    - Universal Card (Mitel Keerz tape). Undated. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 11)
    - Universal Card Discover spots: Border; Baseball; Airport; Whole New Way; Ends of the Earth; Perfectly Clear; 100 Million Dollars; Cash-Back Bonus; Business Trip; Lunchtime Shopping. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 4:30 (Box 11)
    - Vanity versions: Call Anywhere; Provincial Calling. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 22:00 (Box 11)